Hello Hello,
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky, Ukraine, where are you
я из города Хмельницкий Украина Вы
from, the
откуда
city of Belgorod,
город Белгород
the reality of Belgorod is a lot.
реальность Белгорода много Прикалывается
And where do they live now,
меньшая часть А где они живут сейчас
the last time I heard that they were accommodating
последний раз слышал что размещали
refugees
беженцев
[music]
[музыка]
when the Ukrainian side arrives. Here,
когда прилетает украинской стороны Тут
not quite there now, the Russian
не совсем там сейчас орудит русский
volunteer corps is operating here, where in the fact
добровольческий корпус у нас где в том
that we used to have border guards on
что у нас раньше стояли пограничники на
the border Yes, after a year ago you
границе Да после того как год назад вы
broke into our  the country was killed
ворвались в нашу страну поубивали
Border guards at the border we do not
Пограничников на границе мы не
control the border there is a gray zone there
контролируем границу там серая зона там
who wants to go now for example your this
кто хочет ходит сейчас например ваш этот
Russian volunteer corps where
русский добровольческий корпус откуда
he is from Russian Citizens of the Russian Federation
он русский Граждане Российской Федерации
to whom
кому
Show some document Show
Покажите какой-то документ Покажите
Prove that they obey the
Докажите что они подчиняются
foreign
иностранному
Russian Federation Russian
Российской Федерации русский
Volunteer corps is fighting citizens of the
Добровольский корпус воюет граждан
Russian Federation  points that are
Российской Федерации пункты которые
stuck in the Kremlin
засела в Кремле
and why they are in the form of a bolt can you
а почему они носят форму засовы можете
explain in general the form can be bought at
объяснить вообще форму можно купить в
any military store any now it’s not a problem
любом военторге любом сейчас не проблема
NATO equipment can also be traded military equipment of
технику натовскую тоже военную технику
some country could have been
можно военторгнуть какой-то страны могли
captured, look could
захватить смотрите могли
Russian Soldiers could have captured
российские Солдаты могли захватить
NATO equipment of Ukraine And RDK I can
натовскую технику Украины А РДК могу
capture  Russian soldiers
захватить российских солдат
I’m saying that you don’t have
Я говорю что у вас же нету
proof that Ukraine is giving them
доказательства это Украина им дает
equipment Absolutely not,
технику Абсолютно нет
that’s all, that is, look at the equipment, you
вот и все то есть смотрите технику
understand if you have some kind of there, for example, they
понимаете если у вас какой-то там
have planes, for example,
например зайти имеют самолеты например
you that some Russian volunteer
ты что какие-то русские добровольские
corps cannot have any  then there’s a lot of equipment
корпус не может иметь какую-то технику
for now
на сейчас очень просто
Yes, you can buy a tank like this now
куча Да такого сейчас можно танк можете
Yes, that is, and it turns out that we are
купить да то есть и получается что мы
like Ukraine We are very worried that a
как Украина Мы очень обеспокоены что
civil war is taking place near our border We are ready to lead
гражданская война Мы готовы вести
peacekeepers If you ask Yes, for
миротворцев Если вы попросите Да чтобы
example, we can sign, we can act as a
мы например подписали мы можем выступить
guarantor for  you and the Russian
гарантом для вас и российское
Volunteer Russian Volunteer
Добровольческой русского Добровольского
Corps so that you sign the Chisinau agreements with these
корпуса чтобы вы подписали с этими
rebels
повстанцами
Yes there will be
кишиневские соглашения Да там будет
certain clauses yes on the withdrawal of troops on the
определенный пункты да о выводе войск о
Peaceful settlement of this conflict We are
Мирном урегулировании этого конфликта Мы
ready to help but we cannot remember the
готовы помочь но мы не можем помнить
foolish right until you apply
дуронному праву пока вы не Обратитесь
yourself you must ask us and can
Сами вы должны попросить нас и может
to make a peace plan of President
сделать мирный план президента
Zelensky and President Putin to
Зеленского и президента Путина по
resolve the civil conflict in
урегулированию гражданского конфликта в
certain regions of the Belgorod Bryansk
отдельных регионах Белгородской Брянской
regions,
областей
it’s like an official to declare no an
это как официальное лицо заявлять нет
official
официальным лицом Я просто украинец
and
территории своей страны Да вот а
there are also hostilities near our country.
возле нашей страны тоже есть боевые
It is very sad, of course,
действия Это очень печально конечно да
that the Brotherly people began the Brotherly
что у Братского народа началась Братская
civil war. We would not want
гражданская война Мы бы не хотели возле
to have such problem regions near our borders.
своих границ иметь такие проблемные
Yes, that’s why we are watching very closely.
регионы Да поэтому мы очень пристально
then
чтобы эти боевики не бросать через потом
to the territory of Ukraine Yes,
на территорию Украины Да вот
we want you to finally settle it
мы хотим чтобы вы урегулировали наконец
I don’t understand why you are
именно я не понимаю почему вы
shelling your peaceful cities there
обстреливаете свои мирные города там
Shebekino Yes you are evacuating people you can’t
Шебекино Да эвакуируете людей не можете
ensure the safety of the population so that
обеспечить безопасность населения так то
is, it’s very sad yes, that is,
есть это очень печально да то есть
how many people have already died in the Belgorod
сколько уже погибло людей э Белгородской
region,
области сколько
how many  I know, well, you see That is, even you You
не знаю ну вот видите То есть вы даже
live there, you are not interested, you don’t
Вам Вы живете там вам не интересно вы не
think Well, they bomb Shebekino, it means they
считаете Ну бомбят Шебекино значит
are bombing, and the fact that people there do not agree with the
бомбят да то что люди там не согласны с
Putin regime, like, that is, you
путинским режимом типа то есть вам вы их
fill them up with hail
завалите градами
Well Russian volunteer corps Legion of
Ну русский добровольческий корпус Легион
Freedom of Russia
Свободы России
Why terrorists  there is no
Почему террористы нет
Russian Federation that does not agree
Российской Федерации которые не согласны
with the points that are stuck in the Kremlin
с пункты которые засела в Кремле
can be
могут быть
And what did they
А что они
do
сделали
it blew up the metro these are like a militia
это взорвали метро это эти как ополчение
that does not agree with the Moscow regime
которое не согласна с московским режимом
that established its dictatorship
который установил свою диктатуру
presses all the opposition closes TV
прессует всех оппозиты закрывает
channels
телеканалы
for example Rain TV channel
например телеканал Дождь
that
что
everyone avoids Russia from Russia Or  they themselves are
из России все сами избегают Или сами
dying
умирают
such an interesting conversation
такой интересный разговор
all your processor overheated
все у тебя процессор перегрелся
Pit sand like and comment Slava Ukraine
Пит песка лайк и коммент Слава Украине
subscribed us a kilogram right at a time
подпишлись нами килограмм прям за раз
autumn and buttocks
осень а попок
C more and more important YouTube driving
C дуже и дуже важила его YouTube загоняя
us through quarries into a shadow ban and a
нас через карьерки в теневый бан и
hollowed-out video is not shown to people in
дужебокату видео не показывается людям в
private is not shown  information about
частном не показывается информация про
streams in order to have a little
стримы тому для того чтобы мало
operational whistle, prefer straight at a
оперативный свисток предпочтите прям за
time and try there in a kilogram about Krim
раз а попыт там в килограмме о Крим
video
видео
information and we will
информация и мы с вами
show you
покажем вам
[music]
[музыка]